Oleksii (Oli) Mostovyi

e-mail: mostovoy.alexey@gmail.com

Mobile: 0410 256 252

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/olimstv/ **Address:** Unit 5, 11-17 Walkerville Tce. 5081

OBJECTIVE

Seeking a position where 5 years of experience in software testing can be utilized and add value. I am an energetic team player, who promotes and supports a professional and efficient working environment.

With my outstanding customer service skills, a 'can-do' approach to all tasks, a willingness to develop new skills, and a consistently high level of communication and productivity, I believe I can be a valuable asset to any company who is searching for driven and motivated staff.

SKILLS

Soft skills:

- Passionate about quality
- Well organized
- Excellent problem-solving skills
- Attentive to details
- Good operation and interaction with colleagues
- Work well in both team and autonomous environments
- Able to quickly respond to new challenges
- Willing and able to acquire new skills swiftly.
- Work well under tight deadlines and expectations.
- Able to recognize and prioritize workloads
- Willing to share knowledge and experience, to benefit all.

Technical skills:

- Programming languages:
 - JavaScript
 - o Ruby
 - o SQL
- Frameworks and technologies:
 - Rest API
 - o React
 - Express JS
 - o MongoDB
 - o Node JS
 - Next JS
 - Gatsby
 - o Rails
 - o PostgreSQL
 - o Material UI
- Developer tools:
 - o Eclipse IDE
 - o IntelliJ IDEA IDE
 - o Visual Studio Code
 - o Git
 - o PTC Integrity Lifecycle Manager
 - o DBeaver (relational database tool)
 - o Confluence
 - o Jira

Oleksii Mostovyi **Tel:** 0410 256 252 2 of 7

Software Testing Automation Engineer

GlobalLogic, Lviv Ukraine

Sep 2015 – Jul 2017, and

Nov 2017 - Feb 2019

WORK HISTORY:

- System components and functions analysis
- Reviewing design inputs according to the scope of testing issues
- Creation and updating of UI and Functional Test Cases (manual and automation)
- Creation and updating the Traceability Matrixes
- Writing test cases for defect fix
- Automated test code-review and test stabilization
- Establishing automation testing environment
- Performing iteration analysis and test planning
- Selection and running tests for regression testing
- Reporting defects and monitoring their status until satisfactory resolutions have been implemented
- Performing fixes and build verification
- Change Requests analysis
- Functional testina:
 - Writing test scripts and test scenarios to meet acceptance criteria and quality standards
 - Documenting results of test executions including bug reporting
 - Performing formal testing to provide the results for the Federal Drug Administration (FDA)
 - Reviewing newly created/updated test designs, test cases and test scripts
- Management in sprint planning.
- Participation in knowledge-sharing activities

About company

<u>GlobalLogic</u> is a Digital Product Engineering Services company that was founded in 2000 and is headquartered in San Jose, California. GlobalLogic provides software product development services, including experience design, complex systems engineering, content engineering, and self-contained engineering labs. The company specializes in software engineering for cloud platforms, embedded software, Internet of Things, Automotive, mobile applications, and security.

About projects:

Software testing and reporting for the following:

- <u>MiniMed™ 670G</u> system with SmartGuard™ (automated medical insulin pump).
- Guardian™ Connect CGM (Continuous Glucose Monitoring) Mobile App.

Quality Assurance Test Engineer

Rolique, Lviv Ukraine Jul 2017 – Nov 2017

- Analysing client requests for validity and feasibility
- Analysis of acceptance criteria to determine future development and testing activities for product concepts.
- Writing test scripts and test scenarios to meet acceptance criteria with strong focus on maintaining high quality standards
- Prepare assessment data to be used in product testing.
- Documenting results of test execution and bug reporting
- Participation in acceptance testing
- Creation and reviewing of product requirements, specifications and technical design documents
- Performing fixes and build verification
- Performing fortnightly demos for presentation to the product owners

About Company:

<u>Rolique</u> is a web development company, originally founded in Lviv, Ukraine. The company designs and develops mobile and web products for the businesses of EU (INTERMATE, IKEA etc).

About project:

CRM web application for the "INTERMATE Media GmbH" company. Provides a variety of useful tools for the managers of the company to create, schedule and update all events and activities associated with advertising campaigns for the company's customers.

Quality Assurance Test Engineer QA Light Training Center

Sep 2014 – Aug 2015

- Analyzed business requirements and suggested improvements to the product features
- Developed test cases for functional and regression testing of the project, Actify.
- Tested functional modules such as Home Page, Dashboard Page, Content Elements, Registration, My Profile, Friends, Places List, Activity, Messages
- Tested implementation of social networking features: blog, forum, instant messaging, new feeds
- Validated application's GUI for compliance with Usability guidelines published by US Department of Human Services

- Participated in cross-browser (MSIE, Firefox, Chrome, Safari) and cross-platform (Windows 8/7/XP, MAC OS X) testing in virtual machine (VMWare) environment
- Analyzed software failures, made them reproducible, reported bugs

About Company:

<u>QA Light</u> is an IT training centre, originally founded in Kiev, Ukraine. The company is one of the leaders of IT education market in Ukraine. Also provides variety of outsourcing services in testing of SW products for the IT companies on domestic and European market.

About project:

"Actify" - Social Event Discovery Platform – a web-based platform that delivers content and information on entertainment and business events within Europe.

EDUCATION/ TRAININGS/ CERTIFICATES

Additional education and training:

Currently finishing Full-Stack Web Development Online course at "General Assembly" (Software Engineering Immersive program).

2015 - 2018, GlobalLogic training:

- Linux
- Effective Project Management
- Bluetooth protocol
- Agile SDLC Methodologies
- JavaScript (Advanced)
- Being Productive (A training course covering methods of developing appropriate work skills and using best practices on being productive autonomously as well as in teams)

2014, QA Light Training Centre:

- Networking
- Software Testing and Quality Assurance
- SQL (Structured Query Language)

Donetsk Music College

- Music Art
- Drumming
- Percussionist

LANGUAGES

- English Upper Intermediate level (IELTS score 6.5)
- Ukrainian, Russian native speaker

Oleksii Mostovyi **Tel:** 0410 256 252 6 of 7

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Hobbies and Interests Music

- Drummer in several past bands
- Drum Teaching
- Learning to play:
 - o Indian flute
 - o Piano
 - Guitar
- Sound engineering and video production

Psychology

- Researching different schools of psychology (biological, behavioral, cognitive, social)
- Attended several online personal development training courses

Sport

- Athletics
- Swimming
- Cycling

REFERENCES

- Oleksandr Bilyk **Team Lead** oleksandr.bilyk@globallogic.com
- Dmytro Porfirov Project Manager <u>dmytro.porfirov@glo</u>ballogic.com
- Adrian Gravelle Teaching Technologist University of South Australia adrian.gravelle@unisa.edu.au 0434 549 598

Oleksii Mostovyi **Tel:** 0410 256 252 7 of 7